Koreans!
Yeah!
Is that Korean?
Did you fry up some takanmari?
Wow!
Nice!
Yeah!
My first taste!
It's Yadayo's game!
It's Yadayo!
Yadayo!
It's a bow!
Whoo!
Huh?
No!
No, this one!
Hello everyone! I'm Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love
and Moeko Tanizawa of NOT EQUAL ME
Saya Tanizaki and
Emi Ozawa from MIRROR Equal J!
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
So, we are the four members of the mixed group.
Do you remember me?
Do you remember?
It was on July 7, at POMO's distribution.
We played various games.
Tanizawa's team won!
Wow!Wow!
That's when you get your reward.
You got it.
I got it.
But that time, you chose something like a domestic trip.
We chose gourmet food, right?
You took a day trip, a gourmet trip.
You chose the fishing industry fishing industry.
But, oh my God!
What?
This reward just got a whole lot more powerful!
There will be Koreans!
Yay!
Korea?
I'm in Korea!
Korea!
Wow!
We are all going to have dinner tonight!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
This is my first time to eat Korean food!
Really!
And it's already right in front of me right now.
What a surprise!
I got takkan mari!
I've always wanted to try takkan mari!
Have you ever had it?
It's my first time!First time.
Well then, it's everyone's first time.
Today's video is just about having a delicious dinner in Korea!
It's a real treat!
All I see is a recorder or something.
Cocolo! Cocolo!
Wait, what else did we do?
Kokoro! Kokoro!
Thank you so much.
I'm so glad to be here for the final show.
Not only this video today, but we're planning to shoot a lot more in Korea.
I hope you all look forward to what's to come after this!
First of all, dinner!
Bon appétit!
Can we eat this already?
I can eat it.
Is there tteokbokki in it?
Ddeokbokki?
It's so good!
It's in!
Yes!
It's good!
It's so good!
Meat and ddeokbokki!
Looks so good!
Ddeokbokki is amazing!
Amazing!
They're all here.
Yes! Yes!
Let's eat!
Ready!
Bon appétit!
My first takkan mari!
Yum!
Tasty?
Soft!
Juicy!
Yum!
Good? May I?
Well, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to go get some meat.
Eat up!
The sauce goes so well with it!
You're right.
It's good!
Yes! My first taste!
Wow! It's so good!
Let's close it up! Let me get the bird!
I don't know! Bon appétit!
With green onions! Yum!
Delicious!
It's the hardest thing in the world!
So cute! Delicious!
Delicious!Delicious!
It's really good!
How about we play a little game here?
Game?
I mean, we are traveling in Korea tomorrow.
We are going to play a game of dress-up tomorrow.
We're going to decide what to wear based on price.
400,000 won or 200,000 won?
Something like 40,000 or 20,000 yen.
Wow!
So it's totally different.
It's like they're divided into two teams.
Oh my god, the staff said...
It seems to be here!
By accident!
You've got to be kidding me!
One of the teams will get 400,000 won
And one team gets 200,000 won.
Which one will it be?
The price game.
What game will we play this time?
Saya, can you announce it?
Yes!
It's the Hachidaya game!
Hachidaya game
What's the Hachidaya game?
This is a game I used to play on the radio.
There was a time when I said "No way!
I'm the one who makes you think I don't want to do it.
I say this before the second chorus. Before the second chorus, I'm going to say this.
There's a line that says "I don't want to".
If you say it in Shiritori, you lose!
It's a game called "Shiritori".
Normally, you lose if you say
but if you say "ya", you lose!
but if you say "Ya", you lose.
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
So, for example
Moe-chan says, "Shiritori".
Moe said
I'll say, for example
Monja!
Let's say I say
Then
the next one
Surely monja!
Monja!
It can be done in Shiritori
So it can be done in Shiritori too!
I see!
I'll do it.
If I say "No way", my team loses.
Is this a one-shot game?
If we both lose...
I see.
Will it be over?
I wonder if it's over.
Well, it didn't take me long to finish.I finished rather quickly, didn't I?
Okay, then.
The team that loses by two is called the loser.
I definitely want to hear your "No!
I'll do my best.
I want to hear Saya-chan's!
I want to hear yours.
Who would like to start?
Let's start with me.
Like this.
Like this?
Then...
Let's start with you, Fushigi.
Rivals, rivals!
It's like a twin-code!
A twin-code!
A twin-code showdown!
Not a twin-code?
Let's start with Saya, shall we?
Let's change the order.
When they become rivals...
Okay.
I'd like to start again.
Then we'll start normally.
I'm nervous.
Three.
Apothecary.
Chemist.chemist
apothecary
Medicine, you
Male
ницу
Wolf
Laithelyte
Sazura
Tat.
ch
aliment
Korea
Water
Lilith
watermelon
Ka
capsicum (Capsicum annuum, Capsicum annuum, etc.)
watermelon (esp. as a refreshing drink)
bear (esp. the Japanese bear, Ursus arctos arctos)
mama
again and again
pillow
school bag
Ruby
Now
Now!
Pine. Pine. Pine of the pine tree.
Did you say piles of wood? Piles of trees.
Wood? Here we go again.
I don't mind dolphins at all.
Persimmon, chrysanthemum...
Persimmon, car.
Ma, Mike.Ma Mike
Apples Sesame
Maracas, Sushi.
What? I'm out.
No, no, no, no.
Elementary school.
What?
Cow.
The island.
Oh, no! It won't come out!
Cow.
Mai...
Maiko.
Maiko!
Ma-chan
No, no, no, no.
Maiko
Mabba
Mal
Mavamalu?
Le Le Le Le
Rouge?
Rouge.
Rouge.Rouge.
Yoo.
Yoo
Yoo. Yoo. Yoo. Yoo. Miyo.
zwei No!
Me.
Oh, one... I'll get eaten.
I've got to be somewhere else.
I can't think of anything else when I'm doing it.
Well done.
If I win, we'll go on once more.
You're right, you're right.
Let's give it a shot.
Then be conscious of putting arrows on it.
Itoiii JOY
yes
No, no, no...
No!
What?
Huh? Is that it?
Yes? No?
No? Yes?
Yes!
Hitomi.
I'll leave the rest to you.
The finals.
I'm in the finals of the shepherd's final.I am a finalist for the sheaths
Hitomi
I'll do my best
Okay, Takanmari
Ri
Ri Ri Ri
I made a mistake again!
Ruby
Ruby.
Huh?
No...
No, no, no.
No.
No bread.
No, I don't like it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Dog.
Dog
snugly
lickety-split
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is what we've come to.
Lukewarm. Lukewarm. Lukewarm.
Here we go. Ten seconds. Ten seconds.Here we go. 10 seconds. 10 seconds.
Nice try, sleepyhead.
Why can't it be warm?
I don't question it.
Okay, no question, sleepyhead.
Ears.
Ears
Ear tabs
Pig
Pig?
Treasure Treasure
Treasure
The thing.
That's why I caught the thing.
That's why I captured the thing
We've got the thing.
What? What?
What?
A groove.
It's a groove.
Watch out.
Remind me.
They do that a lot.
Drum
Mook
Nostalgic
Grass
You said grass in my voice.You said grass in my voice.
I said grass.
The prairie grass.
So prairie grass.
Grassy grass.
You were sloppy, weren't you?
Yes, I did, didn't I?
Five seconds.
You look happy.
Come on.
Whisper it.
What?
Everyone.
Everyone!
I guess.
It just popped into my head.
Nappa
Sasami
Wait a minute... do you have a stretcher?
Stretcher?
Myan.
Ma.
I didn't see any.
There it is!
That's it.That's it!
Myanmar.
He's talking about Myanmar.
Ma.
White.
Ma
MAH
Mat
Mar At
La
Bublы
Name
Ma
MaMa
Maa.
It's all déjà vu.
Oh no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's all of them... all of them... all of them...
I'm sure it's a great echo.
In tomorrow's picture coding showdown, this team will pay 400,000 yen for 400,000, and the re-creation team will pay 200,000 yen for 200,000, for about 20,000 yen.
I'll try my best.
Thank you very much.
So, please look forward to the next video, and thank you again for watching today.
Ending
Please subscribe to our channel!